{
  "solutionsdata": [
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "question": "Cero"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "question": "Uno"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "question": "Dos"
    },
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "question": "Tres"
    },
    {
      "answer": "4",
      "question": "Cuatro"
    },
    {
      "answer": "5",
      "question": "Cinco"
    },
    {
      "answer": "6",
      "question": "Seis"
    },
    {
      "answer": "7",
      "question": "Siete"
    },
    {
      "answer": "8",
      "question": "Ocho"
    },
    {
      "answer": "9",
      "question": "Nueve"
    }
  ]
}